Contact

nursezike@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jennifer-zike-koller-68a2584a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Critical Care Inpatient ACLS

Jennifer Zike Koller

Travel Nurse at SpringBoard Healthcare

Greater Indianapolis

Summary

Experienced Cardiac Catheterization Laboratory Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the Hospital & Health Care industry. Skilled in Medical Devices, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Patient Safety, Acute Care, and Nursing. Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate of Science (A.S.) focused in Nursing Science from Excelsior College.

Experience

SpringBoard Healthcare
Travel Nurse
July 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)

St Francis
Cardiac cath lab nurse
January 2010 - July 2019 (9 years 7 months)

Education

Excelsior College

Associate of Science (A.S.), Nursing Science · (2006 - 2006)